Merit week is when comp teams find out
who's below range, which managers earn
less than their team, and what it'll cost
to fix. ShiftWorks HR gives you a
prioritized review queue and leadership
PDF from one roster upload — in under a
minute.
Pull your roster from Workday, ADP, or any
spreadsheet — no new HRIS, no API. Drop it
into ShiftWorks HR and you're ready to go.
No configuration or implementation.
Right away you get a review queue ranked
by severity — what's critical, what's high
priority, and what to tackle before merit
letters go out.
You also get the dollars — what it costs
to fix underpaid employees, your merit
pool, and total budget exposure. So when
finance asks, you have an answer.
Every flag comes with names, departments,
and exact dollar gaps — not just a row
count buried in a spreadsheet.
Awkward manager situations get caught too
— when someone earns less than the people
they manage, you see both names and
salaries side by side.
When leadership asks about pay fairness,
you see median pay by gender and race —
and the dollar gap between groups, pulled
straight from your roster.
If your roster includes work location,
ShiftWorks HR shows median pay by city and
what share of your team is in each —
geographic pay patterns without another
spreadsheet.
Need to brief executives? One click gives
you a summary with risk level, total
exposure, and the talking points they'll
actually ask about.
Try ShiftWorks HR free with your own
roster. No credit card required.